<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Task4 - Eichberger, Schiffer, Siuka, Sprenger, Zieger</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Task4 - Eichberger, Schiffer, Siuka, Sprenger, Zieger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 21:41:23 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Content Strategy</title>
      <link>/posts/about-content-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 21:41:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/about-content-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Content Strategy A Master&amp;rsquo;s programme at the FH Joanneum in Graz The web has turned companies into media companies. As a result, there is a need for first-class content strategists. Our part-time degree course is the first academic programme in Europe which trains students for this role. Join us and help establish content strategy as a discipline for the methodical development of web content in the German-speaking world.
You can also find all information about this degree programme at: Content Strategy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About COS20 Students</title>
      <link>/posts/about-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 21:41:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/about-students/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our personal site Group Website for Digital Publishing Platform We - Alexandra, Katharina, Markus, Tamara &amp;amp; Xandi - are students at the FH Janneum in Graz and are currently completing the first semester of the Master&amp;rsquo;s programme &amp;ldquo;Content Strategy&amp;rdquo;.
For our Assignment #4 in Digital Publishing Platform, we were asked to create a website that represented our group work. Therefore, we welcome you to our group site.
You will find a short, personal description of ourselves below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
